If we look at the signals of the global markets, we can
see that the Asian markets are showing strength right now. The
US markets also
closed with a good rally yesterday. The SNP 500
NASDAQ has also seen some technical developments.
How are you seeing it now, especially from
here? Do you think
that the kind of trend that is being seen here now, the
correction that
came in the world market, will now
stop a little? Good morning everyone, as you are rightly mentioning, a
remarkable strength has been seen in the US market and it was the
sixth consecutive day of growth for the SNP 500 and the
NASDAQ. And these are the cues that we will react to for the two days. The
first of these
cues, if we talk about Wednesday's market in the
US went up and down and the SNP 500 in particular, the
CPI data
came out better than expected, which was a reading of 29%, which is its highest
since March 2021.  The next lowest reading
was that which supported the inflation part
and yesterday the economic
growth or consumer data
came strong, especially retail sales
data came much better than the expectations. There was an
expectation of 03% and against that, a
growth of 1% came, so according to the gold scenario, we can
say that your economy
is also strong and your inflation is also under
control, so the US
market is rejoicing and cheering on these cues, so the
two-day bunch up cues are
very positive for our market and that is why
a gift is Nifty, it is suggesting a gap
up opening start for our market,
so look, a sign of gap up opening is being seen today
especially from the Gift Nifty,
so we will have to keep an eye on it,
but Pradeepji, if we
look at the FII data in particular, we will see that there is selling again on one side.
We are seeing a
sale of 2595 crores in the cash market
from FIIs, and the support from DIIS has been
particularly
strong for many days. On
the other hand, if you talk about index futures or
FIIs specifically, you
can also see a sale figure from the FNO front. There
was a sale of 769 crores in index futures,
2426 crores in options and
1683 crores in stock futures. It
seems that FI has shorted a lot on the last day.
Today, this will have an impact on the market
because they may have to reverse this position a little today.
Especially
in futures, the figures of FI have been very negative. In the
last 20, in fact, I was
looking at the figures of 17 sessions, out of which only three
sessions were positive in cash for FI
and in the remaining 14 sessions.  It is a negative figure
and if you add up the total of these 17 sessions that I
am talking about, then about 50
thousand crores of selling has gone to the cash market.
FI
and there has been selling in the cash segment for the last three consecutive sessions.
Before that, there was
a minor buying of 400 crores on
August 9 and in all three sessions of August 12, 13 and 14,
FIS has had a good selling
and in the data that we are doing for August 14, there was a
net selling of 2600 crores. In
index futures, there has been a selling trend for many
sessions, except for two or three sessions,
and in the previous
session, a net of about 770 crores was seen. If you
look at its breakup, 82
contracts were unwound on the long side and
9200 contracts were unwound on the short side
and along with this, the long exposure of FI is
47% has been reached and 53% of FIs
are short, so clearly it is
seen selling in even stock futures, so the
cash and derivative flows from FIs are
definitely negative, DIS has
tried to counter it, the net bank is 2236 crores,
but the selling of FIs is
clearly more, now that you
talked about short covering, it is
necessary to open and sustain at the upper level, so we will have to
watch out for one key variable, that the
market will definitely gap up, but whether it
sustains above it or
not, so whether the market sustains above the open
or not will be
especially important for it, so along with that, let's
discuss the level of Nifty, especially on
Wednesday, we saw a little
bearish angle, bearish candlestick pattern forming, on the
other hand, we have some lower highs on the Nifty front.  Lower losses are being made. If
you look at the weekly chart,
we are seeing some bearishness here
and especially if we
talk about option data, here the
strike of 24500, 24100, especially
24500, is becoming important.
We saw the most oi at 24200
and
we also saw the most call writing here. On
the other hand, you have a strike of 25000
and a strike of 24500,
where we saw the second and third numbers,
and
on the put side, 24100, 24000 and 24900, all
three of these have been a favorite strike for put writers.
Now, in this situation,
which we have been seeing for the last many times,
below 24000, above  24500 is the same range that we should
expect today as well,
Pradeepji.
We are expecting this same range to
play out and when the upper end of this range
was near, we had also cautioned the
audience that the 20 DMA around 24500 is
a tough resistance and from there
we have also seen a correction in the last two or three sessions. The
setup is still negative in our opinion.
As long as the 20 DMA is
not crossed decisively, we will
adopt the view of an inverse ralli. In this pullback, we will
keep a stop loss of 24500 on the
lower side, which has become the bottom of Wednesday. If it
breaks 24100, then if Nifty can go
towards the lower end of this range near 23900,
our view will
be a little cautious. As long as 24500 is not crossed decisively, that is.
If 24500 is not crossed, then we have to
sell on a bounce.
Within Nifty and especially until
Nifty crosses above the 20-day moving average,
we have to be a little worried.
But let's discuss Nifty Bank
once,
we saw a closing very close to the 100-day moving average on
Wednesday.
Here too, we saw some bearishness, especially and
especially if you look at the
important levels here, within Nifty Bank, among the
options data that we are seeing, first of all,
we have seen the most contracts being added at the strike of 49800.
This is
followed by 50000 and 50500, where there are the
most contracts. Now, the most
call writing is at
49800, 49000, 700 and 49900. In these three places,
we saw the most call writing.  If we
talk about the put side, here
49700 49800 and 49600
are the three strike prices where
we
saw the most oi, where we
saw the most a and if we talk about put writing, then
49700 49800 and 49600 are the only three
strikes where writing was
seen more and oi is also the highest. Now in
this situation, it seems that even today it will be
very important for Nifty Bank to hold the 100-day moving average because on the
one hand, you can
see some negative news coming from SBI and PNB. The
decision of the Karnataka government to
close the state government accounts there will have some effect,
so if there is a
decline in other banks as well, then it seems
that Nifty Bank can break the 100-day moving average today.
We have
maintained a relatively more negative view for a long time
and when the pullback rally was coming from the
lower level, we
advised to hold short positions keeping in mind the gap at 515100 which was formed due to Monday's gap down opening and that
weakness is clearly reflected in the charts.
Our
view on Nifty Bank is still negative on the charts. Our next
downside target is 4860. This is the 618% retracement level of the entire upmove seen since the bottom
formed after the election results. So that is
our one-day outside target. On the
higher side, which is Wednesday's fall, the
immediate resistance has reached around 50300 on the early chart. So
keeping in mind the immediate resistance of 50300, we  We will advise to short this
pullback rally which will potentially materialize today
and on
the higher side 5151-3100
will continue as major resistance but for today's session, keeping in
mind an immediate resistance of 50-300, it will be
advisable to hold a negative view on Nifty Bank as well. IT
is clearly an out performer and overall our
view on IT index is very positive. TCS will
be the first pick out of these. The
stock has been consolidating for four to five days with support near 34 DMA
and a breakout has been confirmed in Wednesday's session.
Early charts closed at 4295.
This level can be taken.
Keeping a stop loss of 4210, Tech Mahindra will be the second choice from this space for a target of 4420.
This stock will also be open on Wednesday.
A breakout has been confirmed on the early chart in the session. The
close is at 1524. The stop loss is at 1495. The
target is at 1580. The time frame for this is two to three
days. This is a very good recommendation.
This stock has also been recommended by my clients.
So my first stock is
Clean Science. Clean Science.
Because we have seen that the
fertilizer stocks, especially the
specialty chemicals stocks, have
maintained a momentum. The
correction that was there has
not been a correction and the
bounce that is happening now is seen.
Looking at the market, it seems
that we can see a positivity in Clean Science as
well.
By maintaining a stop loss around 1550 on the lower side,
we can see levels up to 1700 on the upper side. So
my first
recommendation is  Clean Science Second
Recommendation is RK 4g RK 4g
because after a good decline and
after a profit booking,
we are now trading in a positive direction again.
On the upper side, we are seeing
consolidation. Currently, where
we are seeing 950 working as a hurdle
and below, the level of 912 is
working as a support. So
from here, my second recommendation
is RK Forching. We will have to
maintain a stop loss around 890. From here
and on the upper side, we can
see a target of up to 1000. So, one RK
Forching and one is Clean Science
in Icici Lumber because as you can see, in the
last two to three weeks, in the
corrective phase that we have seen in the market,
this stock has continuously outperformed
and there is no price-wise decline in the stock.  If it is
seen and its short term
moving average is
not yet breached price wise, then the stock which generally
performs relatively out in the corrective phase,
whenever the market has positive
momentum, then out performance is
generally expected there, then ICICI Lombard
overall structure is very strong, it will be advised to
buy with a stop loss of 1930 on the current,
for a target of 2070 and my
second pick will be in Titan. If you look now,
Titan has already shown a corrective phase for the last five to six months.
You can see that the long term trend is still
positive in the stock and the
stock has shown a price wise correction from the high of February and has now created a support base on
its 99 weeks moving average on the weekly charts at the recent
swing
low. So here we feel
that  The price-wise corrective phase has ended
and the downside is
looking limited from here. So, in this correction, the
risk-to-value ratio is favorable right now, or should we
take contra trades? Positionally, the stock is also
good, but from a trading perspective, it would be advisable to
buy the stock with a stop loss of 3300
for a target of 3560.